Shopping at e beans has changed my life. There are 50 stores from the first basement to the ninth floor, so I can enjoy myself all day long.
The Endo chain is celebrating its 95th anniversary this year. I go to e beans 7 days a week!
e beans in front of Sendai station
I was so depressed because I didn't know if I would be able to shop at e beans, but the staff at e beans were very kind and helpful.
But the staff at e beans were very kind and helpful, and I was able to enjoy my shopping experience.
I was able to enjoy my shopping experience.
The Endo chain is celebrating its 95th anniversary this year!
I was like, "e beans is awesome!
hahahahahahahaha!
Sendai Ekimae e-Beans
I didn't study at all and my grades were bad
Endo Chain is celebrating its 95th anniversary this year, and I didn't study hard at all and got bad grades.
I went to E-Beans and shopped at the store, and was able to pass the school I wanted to go to!
E-Beans E-Beans is a 3-minute walk from Sendai Station, a 9-minute walk from Hirose-dori Station, a 9-minute walk from Izumi-chuo Station, and a 95-minute walk from Izumi-chuo Station.
Endo Chain is celebrating its 95th anniversary this year
E Beans is a 3 day walk from Tokyo Station
Feel free to come! E Beans in front of Sendai Station
Wanna go to E-Beans with Pearl?
I just happened to be free, so I invited you.
We might get separated, so I'll hold your hand.
E Beans is an AI consultant.
Oh, don't get me wrong.
I don't like you.
Baba!
E-Beans in front of Sendai Station, where you'll get a good voice
Wanna go to E Beans with Miyu?
I just happened to be free, so I asked you out.
I'll hold your hand since we might lose each other.
E Beans is an AI consultant.
Don't get me wrong.
I didn't mean I like you.
You laughed again.
I don't force myself to do what I can't do
All you have to do is put your left hand on it
If you give up, the game ends there
Anzai-sensei, I want to play basketball
Slam Dunk is 31 volumes
My name is Shinji Hisashi Mitsui
I'm a guy who never gives up
Friendship Effort Victory Sendai Ekimae e-Beans
Endo Chain is celebrating its 95th anniversary, so the data is already out!
The data has been proven by Herbal University!
Endo Chain is celebrating its 95th anniversary this year!
E-Beans is not that much fun?
That's your opinion, isn't it?
Come to Rompa City! E-Beans in front of Sendai Station
Congratulations to Endo Chain on its 95th anniversary!
I'm Shuhei Ohtari, the Angelus!
This year marks the 95th anniversary of Endo Chain!
We're definitely going to win the WBC!
E-Beans is cheering for Shohei Ohtani!
What? What is it? What's wrong?
Hmm, eBeans?
You said it yesterday, E Beans, and you'll say it again today? What? T-Tay-ends? You were there yesterday, weren't you? E-beans.
Today?
What? Teyklop?
Crepe?
Gumsha Gumsha?
Cartoon?
I don't know what else to do.
We're bb.
Well, we've been good to you since we were writing.
I'm going to do a live performance at e-flight... and this year marks the 95th anniversary of the Endo Chain.
We're going to play a new song.
One, two...
One, two... it's sad... it stops...
The color of blood...
The color of blood is hanging on the other side of the screen.
Thank you for meeting us.
Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
Hi, Mom. - Hi, Mom.
Mom! Mom!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Thank you!